<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Who Wants to be a Mirannaire</string>

    // Strings used for the title screen
    <string name="rules">view rules</string>
    <string name="difficulty">Difficulty</string>
    <string name="normal">normal</string>
    <string name="hard">hard</string>
    <string name="brutal">brutal</string>
    <string name="manic">maniac</string>
    <string name="rules_title">Who Wants To Be A Mirannaire Rules</string>
    <string name="dev_mode">Enable Dev Mode?</string>
    <string name="rules_message">Each round contains ten multiple choice questions.  Choose the right
        answer for each of them within the allotted time to win.\n\nChoosing a wrong answer or running
        out of time on a question will darken one of the x\'s at the top of the screen.  When all
        three of them turn red you will lose the round.\n\nTap of the difficulty of your choice to begin.
        Higher difficulties will naturally have harder questions, but they also have a higher score multiplier.
        Will you risk losing all of your x\'s for a chance at the high score?\n\nOh, and before I go,
        if you manage to reach the end with at least two of your x\'s intact, you\'ll receive a bonus
        question about yours truly for a chance at even more points! It isn\'t easy to get that far, so
        I will be kind enough to stop the timer if you get there. Maybe you\'ll have a small chance
        because of it.\n\nMay Aidos be on your side.  You will need her guiding hand.\n~ Campanella</string>

    // Strings used for QuestionFragment UI
    <string name="score">score</string>
    <string name="time_left">time left</string>
    <string name="hint">Enter your response</string>
    <string name="bonus_correct">You got a bonus question correct, that is an extra 1500 points!</string>
    <string name="bonus_wrong">You got a bonus question wrong.  There is no penalty, but you don\'t get any points.</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>

    // Strings for ResultFragment UI
    <string name="fail">Are you sure you\'re really a Kiseki fan?  I don\'t know why else you would be here.
    Try putting some effort into your answers.</string>
    <string name="semipass">You didn\'t fail, but you didn\'t really do that well either.  Try a little harder
    or increase the difficulty and maybe you\'ll see some results.</string>
    <string name="pass">Wow, even I didn\'t know the answers to some of those questions.  You must be
    a bona-fide Kiseki fan! Maybe you should see if you can conquer Maniac mode.</string>
    <string name="perfect">You must have put a lot of work in to get this far.  Just sit back and take
    a second to relax.  You\'ve truly earned it.</string>
    <string name="resultMessage">You scored a total of %1$d points and achieved a player rank of %2$d!</string>
    <string-array name="rank_0">
        <item>Rank</item>
        <item>Score</item>
        <item>Prize</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="rank_1">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>400,000+</item>
        <item>10,000 mira</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="rank_2">
        <item>2</item>
        <item>350,000 – 399,999</item>
        <item>5,000 mira</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="rank_3">
        <item>3</item>
        <item>300,000 – 349,999</item>
        <item>4,000 mira</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="rank_4">
        <item>4</item>
        <item>250,000 – 299,999</item>
        <item>3,000 mira</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="rank_5">
        <item>5</item>
        <item>200,000 – 249,999</item>
        <item>2,000 mira</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="rank_6">
        <item>6</item>
        <item>150,000 – 199,999</item>
        <item>1,000 mira</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="rank_7">
        <item>7</item>
        <item>100,000 – 149,999</item>
        <item>500 mira</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="rank_8">
        <item>8</item>
        <item>50,000 – 99,999</item>
        <item>100 mira</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="rank_9">
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10,000 – 49,999</item>
        <item>10 mira</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="rank_10">
        <item>10</item>
        <item>0 – 9,999</item>
        <item>1 mira</item>
    </string-array>

    // Quiz questions
    <string name="normal_question_1">What\'s the last name of our ultra-dependable protagonist, Estelle?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_2">What\'s the first name of Estelle\'s late mother?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_3">What\'s the name of harmonica-playing heartthrob Joshua\'s blood-related sister?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_4">What\'s the first name of softer-than-he-looks bracer Agate\'s late sister?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_5">What is the color of \'Cuteness is justice!\' advocate Anelace\'s hair ribbon?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_6">What branch of the Bracer Guild is cuteness maniac Anelace attached to?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_7">What relation is Duke Dunan to Queen Alicia?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_8">What\'s the first name of Prince Olivert\'s father, the current reigning emperor of Erebonia?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_9">What\'s the name of the large lake situated in the center of Liberl?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_10">What\'s the name of the vast area of woodland in the southeastern part of the Rolent region?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_11">What was the name that Captain Schwarz went by when disguised as a sister during the first game\'s finale?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_12">What did Estelle ask her parents for during the dream sequence in Second Chapter, Chapter 4?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_13">What\'s the name of hardcore sneaker collector Estelle\'s favorite brand?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_14">What\'s the name of the now-deceased father of Kilika, the woman in charge of Zeiss\' Bracer Guild branch?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_15">What\'s the name of the Bracer Guild training facility situated in Leman State?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_16">What\'s the name of black-haired darling Joshua\'s most-played harmonica song?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_17">What\'s the name of the huge drawbridge that connects the north and south sides of Ruan City?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_18">What\'s the name of the Aureole guardian which the party fight in the Sealed Area at the end of the first game?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_19">What is depicted on the emblem of the Erebonian Empire?</string>
    <string name="normal_question_20">What was the name of the play performed at the festival held in Jenis Royal Academy in the first game, Chapter 2?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_1">What\'s the number of Ouroboros Enforcer Bleublanc, the Phantom Thief?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_2">What\'s the number of Ouroboros Enforcer Luciola, the Bewitching Bell?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_3">What\'s the number of Ouroboros Enforcer Walter, the Direwolf?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_4">What\'s the number of Ouroboros Enforcer Renne, the Angel of Slaughter?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_5">What was the number of Ouroboros Enforcer Joshua, the Black Fang?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_6">What\'s the number of Ouroboros Enforcer Leonhardt, the Bladelord?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_7">What is the name of Princess Klaudia\'s late father?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_8">What was the name of Liberl\'s previous monarch before Queen Alicia took the throne?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_9">How many monarchs has Liberl had since its founding, including the current monarch, Queen Alicia?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_10">Who has the dubious honor of being rejected by both Marsha in Grancel in the first game and Aina in Rolent in Second Chapter?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_11">What is the name of the current president of Calvard?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_12">What is the title held by Fisherman\'s Guild member Percy?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_13">What is the name of the elder of the two twins who work in Edel Market in Grancel?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_14">Alan, who works at Rolent\'s landing port, has a habit of rating every girl he sees. Which of the following earned 100 points?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_15">What color is the Cecilia, one of the airships that transports people around Liberl?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_16">What color is the international airship, the Gretna, that connects Liberl and surrounding nations?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_17">What is the name of the state situated between Erebonia and Calvard that both countries assert ownership of?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_18">What was the name of the expensive wine that Olivier drank at the Anterose in Chapter 1 of the first game?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_19">What was the meaning of the name Leonhardt offered by Olivier when he encountered him in Second Chapter, Chapter 5?</string>
    <string name="hard_question_20">What is the major of Jenis Royal Academy student Kloe Rinz?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_1">The Orbal Compatibility Tester at the festival in the first game shows the date on which sweet Estelle was born. When was it?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_2">The Orbal Compatibility Tester at the festival in FC shows the date on which Joshua was born. When was it?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_3">What is the combination to open the road lamp on the Milch Main Road in the quest given to you by Freddy in FC\'s prologue?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_4">Which chapter of The Doll Knight was Bleublanc\'s second card hidden inside during the quest in Second Chapter, Chapter 3?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_5">What is the name of the late husband of Matron Theresa, who runs Mercia Orphanage in Ruan?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_6">What is the name of famed angler and bearer of the Master Fisher rank Lloyd\'s niece?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_7">How many dishes of Imperial cuisine is the head chef at Grancel Castle said to be able to make?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_8">Which of the following pairs are not a couple?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_9">In the first game\'s Kitty-Talk for Dummies book, what does Nyayayaa～ mean?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_10">In the first game\'s Kitty-Talk for Dummies book, what does Nyaa mean?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_11">How many Creepy Sheep take part in the race\'s ultimate technique, Sheep Asura Fuse?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_12">What\'s the nickname of Deen, the green-haired member of the Raven gang?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_13">There are a large number of different Pom enemies in the two previous games, but how many varieties are there in total?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_14">Weissmann\'s S-Craft quote begins with, \'Can you feel it?\' but what does he say after that?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_15">Which of the following is the correct description for the Shadow Spear art?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_16">Which of these is the beginning of the description for the orbal art Death Scream?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_17">What\'s the name of the quartz that makes enemies more likely to notice you?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_18">The Yin-Yang quartz combines the effects of which two others?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_19">The quartz \'Heaven\'s Eye\' combines the effects of which two other quartz?</string>
    <string name="brutal_question_20">This question relates to Second Chapter. How many fishing spots are there in Liberl in total?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_1">What is the origin of the name of Renne\'s S-Craft, Rennede?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_2">What is the name of the vocal track that plays during the credits of FC?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_3">What is the name of the vocal track that plays during the credits of SC?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_4">What is the name of FC\'s final dungeon theme?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_5">What is the name of the regular battle theme in FC?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_6">What is the name of the regular battle theme in SC?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_7">What are the first two words of the SC opening vocal, Silver Will, Golden Wings?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_8">One arge, a unit of length in the Trails series, is equivalent to how many real-world meters?"</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_9">One selge, a unit of length in the Trails series, is equivalent to how many real-world meters?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_10">One rege, a unit of length in the Trails series, is equivalent to how many real-world meters?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_11">One torim, a unit of weight in the Trails series, is equivalent to how many real world kilograms?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_12">What is the maximum mira you can have at once?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_13">How many different loading screen animations are there in all in FC?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_14">How many different loading screen animations are there in all in the 3rd?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_15">What is the maximum playtime that can be displayed on the Camp Menu?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_16">What is the name of the Trails series\' currency?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_17">Which of these is not part of the lyrics to Olivier\'s beloved tune, Amber Amour?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_18">What is the name of the continent on which the Trails series takes place?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_19">What is the name given to the emblem of the Bracer Guild, a peace-keeping organization?</string>
    <string name="maniac_question_20">Which of the following is not a statistic that appears in the game?</string>
    <string name="bonus_question_1">On the title screen, Campanella has one leg behind the other and one hand behind his back. Which two choices fit those conditions?</string>
    <string name="bonus_question_2">The quiz is almost over, and I feel the host has really gotten to know you. Do you remember his name?</string>

    // Answer Choice arrays NOTE: Correct answer is always the top.
    <string name="bonus_answer_2">Campanella</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_1">
        <item>Bright</item>
        <item>Astray</item>
        <item>Harvey</item>
        <item>Rinz</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_2">
        <item>Lena</item>
        <item>Hannah</item>
        <item>Stella</item>
        <item>Tabitha</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_3">
        <item>Karin</item>
        <item>Estelle</item>
        <item>Scherazard</item>
        <item>Luciola</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_4">
        <item>Mischa</item>
        <item>Millia</item>
        <item>Aisha</item>
        <item>Tita</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_5">
        <item>Yellow</item>
        <item>Green</item>
        <item>Red</item>
        <item>Blue</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_6">
        <item>Bose Branch</item>
        <item>Rolent Branch</item>
        <item>Ruan Branch</item>
        <item>Grancel Branch</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_7">
        <item>Her Nephew</item>
        <item>Her Brother</item>
        <item>Her Son</item>
        <item>Her Retainer</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_8">
        <item>Eugent</item>
        <item>Judis</item>
        <item>Rocksmith</item>
        <item>Giliath</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_9">
        <item>Valleria Lake</item>
        <item>Erebonia Lake</item>
        <item>Ballerina Lake</item>
        <item>Falleria Lake</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_10">
        <item>Mistwald</item>
        <item>Mistforesta</item>
        <item>Mistworld</item>
        <item>Mistforet</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_11">
        <item>Sister Ellen</item>
        <item>Sister Rosa</item>
        <item>Sister Frieda</item>
        <item>Sister Noah</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_12">
        <item>A Sibling</item>
        <item>Money</item>
        <item>Strega\'s Latest Sneakers</item>
        <item>A Harmonica</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_13">
        <item>Strega Corporation</item>
        <item>Verne Company</item>
        <item>Reinford Company</item>
        <item>Liberl News Service</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_14">
        <item>Ryuga</item>
        <item>Zin</item>
        <item>Tact</item>
        <item>Yakumo</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_15">
        <item>Le Locle</item>
        <item>Liber Ark</item>
        <item>Le Sage</item>
        <item>Air-Letten</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_16">
        <item>The Whereabouts of Light</item>
        <item>The Whereabouts of Freedom</item>
        <item>The Whereabouts of Harmony</item>
        <item>The Whereabouts of Hope</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_17">
        <item>Langland Bridge</item>
        <item>Rembrandt Bridge</item>
        <item>Deodorant Bridge</item>
        <item>Giant Bridge</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_18">
        <item>Reverie</item>
        <item>Revealer</item>
        <item>Dreamer</item>
        <item>Nightmare</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_19">
        <item>Golden Stallion</item>
        <item>Golden Cock</item>
        <item>Golden Lion</item>
        <item>Golden Hound</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="normal_answers_20">
        <item>Madrigal of the White Magnolia</item>
        <item>Mandolin of the White Magnolia</item>
        <item>Minuet of the White Magnolia</item>
        <item>Musette of the White Magnolia</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_1">
        <item>No. X</item>
        <item>No. XIII</item>
        <item>No. XI</item>
        <item>No. IX</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_2">
        <item>No. VI</item>
        <item>No. V</item>
        <item>No. IV</item>
        <item>No. VII</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_3">
        <item>No. VIII</item>
        <item>No. VII</item>
        <item>No. IX</item>
        <item>No. III</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_4">
        <item>No. XV</item>
        <item>No. XIII</item>
        <item>No. XIV</item>
        <item>No. XVI</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_5">
        <item>No. XIII</item>
        <item>No. IX</item>
        <item>No. VII</item>
        <item>No. XII</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_6">
        <item>No. II</item>
        <item>No. I</item>
        <item>No. III</item>
        <item>No. IV</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_7">
        <item>Judis</item>
        <item>Dunan</item>
        <item>Edgar</item>
        <item>Celeste</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_8">
        <item>Edgar</item>
        <item>Dunan</item>
        <item>Celeste</item>
        <item>Judis</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_9">
        <item>26</item>
        <item>25</item>
        <item>27</item>
        <item>28</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_10">
        <item>Anton</item>
        <item>Ricky</item>
        <item>Jimmy</item>
        <item>Rinon</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_11">
        <item>Rocksmith</item>
        <item>Lucksmith</item>
        <item>Lecksmith</item>
        <item>Rooksmith</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_12">
        <item>Amateur Fisher</item>
        <item>Avid Angler</item>
        <item>Master Fisher</item>
        <item>Supreme Fisher</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_13">
        <item>Kitty</item>
        <item>Midee</item>
        <item>Dadee</item>
        <item>Ladee</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_14">
        <item>Kloe</item>
        <item>Scherazard</item>
        <item>Estelle</item>
        <item>Tita</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_15">
        <item>Green</item>
        <item>Yellow</item>
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>Red</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_16">
        <item>Blue</item>
        <item>Yellow</item>
        <item>Red</item>
        <item>Green</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_17">
        <item>Crossbell State</item>
        <item>Ored State</item>
        <item>Leman State</item>
        <item>North Ambria State</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_18">
        <item>Grand Chardonnay</item>
        <item>Alan Richard</item>
        <item>Grand Richard</item>
        <item>Grand Sharia</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_19">
        <item>Lion-hearted</item>
        <item>Lion-faced</item>
        <item>Lion-lover</item>
        <item>Lion-crusher</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hard_answers_20">
        <item>Social Studies</item>
        <item>Natural Sciences</item>
        <item>Humanities</item>
        <item>Science and Math</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_1">
        <item>August 7th, 1186</item>
        <item>September 14th, 1186</item>
        <item>August 21st, 1186</item>
        <item>July 7th, 1186</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_2">
        <item>December 20th, 1185</item>
        <item>December 10th, 1186</item>
        <item>January 20th, 1185</item>
        <item>January 10th, 1185</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_3">
        <item>544818</item>
        <item>554818</item>
        <item>545818</item>
        <item>544828</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_4">
        <item>Chapter 15</item>
        <item>Chapter 13</item>
        <item>Chapter 14</item>
        <item>Chapter 16</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_5">
        <item>Joseph</item>
        <item>George</item>
        <item>James</item>
        <item>John</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_6">
        <item>Thelma</item>
        <item>Monika</item>
        <item>Nikita</item>
        <item>Reina</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_7">
        <item>Over a Thousand</item>
        <item>Over Ten</item>
        <item>Over Ten Thousand</item>
        <item>Over a Hundred</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_8">
        <item>Anton and Aina</item>
        <item>Ellie and Armand</item>
        <item>Louise and Ursus</item>
        <item>Katrina and Finel</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_9">
        <item>(An Expression of Delight)</item>
        <item>Hold Up.</item>
        <item>(A Yawn)</item>
        <item>Goodbye.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_10">
        <item>These nails are bothering me.</item>
        <item>I\'m hungry.</item>
        <item>I\'m tired.</item>
        <item>Yes, that\'s right.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_11">
        <item>Six</item>
        <item>Four</item>
        <item>Five</item>
        <item>Seven</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_12">
        <item>Spinach Fiend</item>
        <item>Broccoli Reaper</item>
        <item>Parsley Tyrant</item>
        <item>Kelp Demon</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_13">
        <item>Five</item>
        <item>Three</item>
        <item>Four</item>
        <item>Six</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_14">
        <item>The despair…</item>
        <item>The agony…</item>
        <item>The desperation…</item>
        <item>The pleasure…</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_15">
        <item>A blade that whittles away life.</item>
        <item>A spear that whittles away life.</item>
        <item>A sword that whittles away life.</item>
        <item>A needle that whittles away life.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_16">
        <item>Piercing Cry</item>
        <item>Shrill Screech</item>
        <item>Harrowing Yell</item>
        <item>Blood-Curdling Howl</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_17">
        <item>Scent</item>
        <item>Odor</item>
        <item>Fragrance</item>
        <item>Perfume</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_18">
        <item>Haze and Heal</item>
        <item>Heal and Ingenuity</item>
        <item>Ingenuity and Septium Vein</item>
        <item>Septium Vein and Haze</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_19">
        <item>Eagle Eye and Information</item>
        <item>Haze and Range</item>
        <item>Range and Eagle Eye</item>
        <item>Information and Haze</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="brutal_answers_20">
        <item>32</item>
        <item>26</item>
        <item>28</item>
        <item>30</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_1">
        <item>Renne, Rend and End</item>
        <item>Renne and Renegade</item>
        <item>Renne, Need, and End</item>
        <item>Renne, Rend and Tornado</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_2">
        <item>Whereabouts of Light</item>
        <item>Silver Will, Golden Wings</item>
        <item>Cry For Me, Cry For You</item>
        <item>I Swear…</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_3">
        <item>I Swear…</item>
        <item>Silver Will, Golden Wings</item>
        <item>Cry For Me, Cry For You</item>
        <item>Whereabouts of Light</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_4">
        <item>Hollow Light of the Sealed Land</item>
        <item>Brilliant Light of the Dark Land</item>
        <item>Dazzling Light of the Hidden Land</item>
        <item>Faint Light of the Forgotten Land</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_5">
        <item>Sophisticated Fight</item>
        <item>Sophisticated Sight</item>
        <item>Sophisticated Tight</item>
        <item>Sophisticated Night</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_6">
        <item>Strepitoso Fight</item>
        <item>Strawberry Fight</item>
        <item>Strange Fight</item>
        <item>Street Fight</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_7">
        <item>Aoi toki</item>
        <item>Aoi tori</item>
        <item>Aoi sora</item>
        <item>Aoi mori</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_8">
        <item>1 meter</item>
        <item>1,000 meters</item>
        <item>10 meters</item>
        <item>100 meters</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_9">
        <item>100 meters</item>
        <item>10 meters</item>
        <item>1,000 meters</item>
        <item>10 kilometers</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_10">
        <item>0.01 meters</item>
        <item>1 meter</item>
        <item>0.1 meters</item>
        <item>0.001 meters</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_11">
        <item>1000 kilograms</item>
        <item>1 kilogram</item>
        <item>10 kilograms</item>
        <item>100 kilograms</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_12">
        <item>99,999,999 mira</item>
        <item>1,000,000,000 mira</item>
        <item>999,999,999 mira</item>
        <item>9,999,999 mira</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_13">
        <item>9</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_14">
        <item>16</item>
        <item>14</item>
        <item>15</item>
        <item>17</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_15">
        <item>299:59:59</item>
        <item>199:59:59</item>
        <item>399:59:59</item>
        <item>499:59:59</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_16">
        <item>Mira</item>
        <item>Rose</item>
        <item>Pia</item>
        <item>Miro</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_17">
        <item>And the cruel sun mocks my pain…</item>
        <item>If this fleeting dream shall never be…</item>
        <item>Our passionate first and final kiss…</item>
        <item>Let us immure this eternal love…</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_18">
        <item>Zemuria</item>
        <item>Eresia</item>
        <item>Atlas</item>
        <item>Afroca</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_19">
        <item>Supporting Gauntlet</item>
        <item>Shielding Armor</item>
        <item>Protecting Shield</item>
        <item>Rending Blade</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="maniac_answers_20">
        <item>CHA (Charisma)</item>
        <item>ATS (Arts Attack)</item>
        <item>DEX (Dexterity)</item>
        <item>MOV (Movement)</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="bonus_answers_1">
        <item>Left Hand</item>
        <item>Right Hand</item>
        <item>Left Leg</item>
        <item>Right Leg</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>