<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OdysseyTourGuide</string>

    // ViewPager Titles
    <string name="kingdoms">Kingdoms</string>
    <string name="npcs">NPCs</string>
    <string name="enemies">Enemies</string>
    <string name="collectibles">Collectibles</string>

    // Kingdom Details
    <string name="landmarks">Landmarks</string>

    // Cap Kingdom
    <string name="cap_name">Cap Kingdom</string>
    <string name="cap_moon_count">31</string>
    <string name="cap_regional_count">50</string>
    <string name="cap_landmark_1">World\'s Best Hat</string>
    <string name="cap_landmark_description_1">This eye-catching tower is famous in Bonneton, both as
        a landmark itself and for the spectacular view from the \"brim.\"\n\nVisitors are allowed inside,
        but many creatures call the tower home, much to the surprise of first timers.</string>
    <string name="cap_landmark_2">Extremely Mobile Homes</string>
    <string name="cap_landmark_description_2">In town, you will immediately notice the unique dwellings
        shaped like hats. These constructions double as both house and airship for the Bonneters, who
        take great pride in them.\n\nSome of the larger \"houseboats\" even have two stories. As private
        dwellings, you can\'t just stroll inside, but the natives don\'t mind people climbing on top
        of their homes. Perhaps being atop private property comes naturally to these hat-like people.</string>
    <string name="cap_landmark_3">A Spectacle of a Bridge</string>
    <string name="cap_landmark_description_3">The bridge that connects the central square and the hills
        is called Glasses Bridge. It\'s a long, double-arched structure whose bottom is hidden in a sea
        of clouds. When you see it, you\'ll understand its affectionate nickname immediately. Many
        tourists enjoy the speedy thrill of rolling across the undulating structure—be sure to give it a try!</string>
    <string name="cap_landmark_4">Old-Fashioned Lighting</string>
    <string name="cap_landmark_description_4">These unique lights only appear in Bonneton. Since the
        area gets so dark every time the moon goes behind the clouds, the lights are designed to be
        switched on with a simple turn of the lantern. The elegant design of these lampposts draws many
        tourists. They\'re even lovelier when turned on, so do give each one a spin as you pass by.</string>
    <string name="cap_landmark_5">The \"Sometimes\" Bridge</string>
    <string name="cap_landmark_description_5">The bridge connecting Central Square to Top-Hat Tower is
        build to retract in an emergency. If this happens during your visit, don\'t panic—just use the
        switch to restore the bridge.</string>
    // Cascade Kingdom
    <string name="cascade_name">Cascade Kingdom</string>
    <string name="cascade_moon_count">40</string>
    <string name="cascade_regional_count">50</string>
    <string name="cascade_landmark_1">A Tall Drink of Water</string>
    <string name="cascade_landmark_description_1">There are many waterfalls in the Cascade Kingdom, but
        the area known as Fossil Falls is a special one.\n\nThere are few sights in nature as grand as
        the millions of gallons of water pouring every second out of this giant triceratops skeleton.</string>
    <string name="cascade_landmark_2">Nature in Balance</string>
    <string name="cascade_landmark_description_2">The stone spire standing near the great falls has
        miraculously remained balanced upright in this position, presumably for eons.\n\nOf particular
        interest are the cubes of unknown material embedded in the stone. These cubes are the reason
        for the common theory that the spire somehow fell from the sky. While this theory is difficult
        to prove, it is equally hard to doubt when looking at this miraculous stone structure.</string>
    <string name="cascade_landmark_3">The Ancient Wall</string>
    <string name="cascade_landmark_description_3">No ordinary cliff face, this structure was carved out
        painstakingly over many long years by people unknown. The wall is composed mainly of fossils,
        and evidence suggests it has been broken many times, causing some to suggest that something is
        buried inside. Visitors are encouraged to explore the mysteries surrounding the Great Barrier,
        if they dare.</string>
    <string name="cascade_landmark_4">The Prehistoric Tyrant</string>
    <string name="cascade_landmark_description_4">The biggest draw for tourists to this area is that
        dinosaurs still live here. Many people willingly put themselves at considerable risk for a
        glimpse of the ancient \"terrible lizards.\"\n\nT-Rex, most terrible of all dinosaurs, can
        pulverize a boulder with a single blow. On the other hand, most people don\'t realize how much
        time they spend napping.</string>
    <string name="cascade_landmark_5">An Old, Odd Structure</string>
    <string name="cascade_landmark_description_5">No one knows how a Bonneton-style structure got buried
        here. Bonneters travel often, so they may have lived here in the past. It is a helpful landmark
        if you get lost, though.</string>
    // Sand Kingdom
    <string name="sand_name">Sand Kingdom</string>
    <string name="sand_moon_count">89</string>
    <string name="sand_regional_count">100</string>
    <string name="sand_landmark_1">Tostarenan Town</string>
    <string name="sand_landmark_description_1">A small town that serves as the hub for tourists planning
        to visit the Inverted Pyramid. The colorful buildings and cheerful people provide a warm welcome
        for visitors. They\'re happy to provide direction, so don\'t hesitate to say hello.</string>
    <string name="sand_landmark_2">Mysterious Ancient Ruins</string>
    <string name="sand_landmark_description_2">Head north from town and you\'ll be greeted by ancient
        ruins that dot the expansive desert. Though many have become conflict regions patrolled by Bullet
        Bills, their status as important heritage sites is undeniable.\n\nYour eye will be drawn to the
        large stone tower at the heart of the ruins. Due to extensive hollowing underground, quicksand
        has become prevalent in this area, so watch out.</string>
    <string name="sand_landmark_3">Inverted Pyramid</string>
    <string name="sand_landmark_description_3">The true \"can\'t miss\" of this region, the Inverted
        Pyramid may look unstable, but rest assured it never topples and has thrilled tourists for years.
        It is said that a legendary artifact called the Binding Band lies within, and the upside-down
        pyramid symbolizes how those joined by it will never part even if the world turns upside down.</string>
    <string name="sand_landmark_4">Jaxi</string>
    <string name="sand_landmark_description_4">Let\'s have a look at the curious local transport method
        known as the Jaxi. Just hop on the back of one, and as you might guess from their appearance,
        you\'ll be in for a wild but completely reliable ride. Make good use of them and you\'ll be
        exploring this unforgiving desert in comfort and style.</string>
    <string name="sand_landmark_5">Living Heart of the Desert</string>
    <string name="sand_landmark_description_5">Here\'s a spot to moisten your dried and withered heart,
        with greenery and water to make you forget you\'re in the desert. The fish and birds are plentiful
        and well worth a visit.</string>
    // Lake Kingdom
    <string name="lake_name">Lake Kingdom</string>
    <string name="lake_moon_count">42</string>
    <string name="lake_regional_count">50</string>
    <string name="lake_landmark_1">The Domed Water Plaza</string>
    <string name="lake_landmark_description_1">Lake Lamode, the land of fashion. The underwater Water
        Plaza is protected by a glass dome, but don\'t worry, there\'s air inside to breathe. When you
        look up at the lake from within the plaza, you can see Dorrie swimming amid the stunning scenery.</string>
    <string name="lake_landmark_2">Window Shopping</string>
    <string name="lake_landmark_description_2">Considered the most luxurious garment this kingdom has
        to offer, the Lochlady Dress is displayed in the show window of the Water Plaza. Of all the garments
        created by the Lochladies, only the very best and most beautiful is selected for this great honor.
        It\'s a national treasure!\n\nIt's said that wearing this dress brings eternal happiness, so
        naturally every bride yearns for it. Sadly, this lovely, one-of-a-kind item is not for sale.</string>
    <string name="lake_landmark_3">Zippers of Mystery</string>
    <string name="lake_landmark_description_3">Fitting of a kingdom famous for its fashion, you can find
        zipper art all over the place here. Zippers can be securely fastened as well as opened and closed
        freely, so perhaps they have a deeper meaning… That said, this particular zipper is more than
        decoration. It actually works, so stop by and give it a try.</string>
    <string name="lake_landmark_4">Dorrie the Aquatic Buddy</string>
    <string name="lake_landmark_description_4">This gentle creature spends its days swimming gracefully
        in Lake Lamode. If you\'re confident in your abilities, swimming alongside it might make for some
        wonderful memories.\n\nAlthough able to live in any aquatic environment, some have heard Dorrie
        complain that the lake is too small. Keep an eye out for Dorrie-themed souvenirs, which tourists just love!</string>
    <string name="lake_landmark_5">Soaked in History</string>
    <string name="lake_landmark_description_5">Once a spot for designers to relax and even dye cloth,
        this soaking pool has a rich history. Since most activity centers around the lake town, this is
        now a well-known fishing hole.</string>
    // Wooded Kingdom
    <string name="wooded_name">Wooded Kingdom</string>
    <string name="wooded_moon_count">76</string>
    <string name="wooded_regional_count">100</string>
    <string name="wooded_landmark_1">The Living Factory</string>
    <string name="wooded_landmark_description_1">No one knows who built the giant machines dotting this land,
        but today the Steam Gardeners use them to maintain the greatest flower gardens in the world.
        The giant dome is climate-controlled and apparently self-sufficient, operating with no maintenance
        since ancient times.</string>
    <string name="wooded_landmark_2">Guardians of Paradise</string>
    <string name="wooded_landmark_description_2">Visitors are welcomed not only by the humid air, but
        worker robots tending the flowers. They\'re known as Steam Gardeners, longtime residents of the
        kingdom. You\'ll be impressed at how long they can work without rest, maintaining themselves
        perfectly. But beyond being hard workers, the robots love flowers—some grow them right out of
        their heads! You\'ll feel the Steam Gardeners\' warm hearts, from their flowers and also their
        internal steam pumps.</string>
    <string name="wooded_landmark_3">Flowers as a Way of Life</string>
    <string name="wooded_landmark_description_3">While you\'ll see amazing flowers on any visit, you
        might be lucky enough to see the famous Steam Gardens Soirée Bouquet. It features giant white
        flowers that charm all who lay eyes on it. As you might guess from the name, it\'s by far the
        most popular bouquet for wedding ceremonies, sought after by wedding planners the world over.</string>
    <string name="wooded_landmark_4">A Deep Wood\'s Secret</string>
    <string name="wooded_landmark_description_4">It doesn\'t appear on any tours, but there is an area
        untouched by the machines of the Steam Gardens. Here the trees grow quickly, barely allowing
        any light through. The Steam Gardeners do not speak of it, but rumor has it they discourage
        visiting this place because of the danger posed by the giant creatures that call it home.</string>
    <string name="wooded_landmark_5">A Growing Walkway</string>
    <string name="wooded_landmark_description_5">Be sure to try the system of paths called the Flower
        Road. You\'ll marvel at plants growing into temporary but walkable bridges. Watch your step,
        though—nature has no handrails.</string>
    // Cloud Kingdom
    <string name="cloud_name">Cloud Kingdom</string>
    <string name="cloud_moon_count">9</string>
    <string name="cloud_landmark_1">Life Above the Clouds</string>
    <string name="cloud_landmark_description_1">Perhaps everyone has had the experience of looking up
        in the clouds and imagining what it would be like to live among them. As it turns out, as
        fantastical as it may sound, there was once such a kingdom whose citizens looked down on the
        world from a fluffy, puffy paradise.</string>
    <string name="cloud_landmark_2">Strangely Floaty Material</string>
    <string name="cloud_landmark_description_2">While the particles that make up a cloud are extremely
        small and light, researchers have recently discovered a kind of cloud-like material that one can
        walk on. First discovered in Fossil Falls, this substance can change into and hold new shapes and
        even support weight.\n\nThe discovery prompted certain researchers to open an investigation into
        whether there might have once been a \"cloud kingdom\" in the sky.</string>
    <string name="cloud_landmark_3">Vestiges of Greatness</string>
    <string name="cloud_landmark_description_3">Once researchers started looking for places in the sky,
        they quickly found a large platform of the levitating substance, dubbed Nimbus Arena.\n\nMysteriously,
        the land had markings that accurately showed the waxing and waning phases of the moon. Now, besides
        the obvious \"how,\" researchers had to question \"why?\"</string>
    <string name="cloud_landmark_4">Giant Cloud Arches</string>
    <string name="cloud_landmark_description_4">Researchers are thus baffled by the large cloud archway
        here. Some theorize that it\'s a kind of reticule that aligns with the moon. Some evidence suggests
        that the arch pulled this kingdom\'s Moon Rock to a specific location from the moon.\n\nThe only
        certainty is that the Cloud Kingdom will continue to interest researchers for many years.</string>
    <string name="cloud_landmark_5">Shower of Flowers</string>
    <string name="cloud_landmark_description_5">The investigation is concluded now and yielded few undisputed
        facts. But the bits of cloud that fall like flower petals here make it the most dreamlike place
        you\'ll ever visit.</string>
    // Lost Kingdom
    <string name="lost_name">Lost Kingdom</string>
    <string name="lost_moon_count">35</string>
    <string name="lost_regional_count">50</string>
    <string name="lost_landmark_1">A Dense, Primeval Forest</string>
    <string name="lost_landmark_description_1">Few visit these remote islands surrounded by poison, but
        they are dense with plants that have followed a unique evolutionary path. There is a strange
        unity between the vibrantly colored plants, the odd animals, and the sea of poison surrounding them.</string>
    <string name="lost_landmark_2">Nature\'s Traffic Lights</string>
    <string name="lost_landmark_description_2">The Tropical Wigglers found here are not aggressive and
        are mostly genial and pleasant creatures. You should, however, avoid touching them, for safety\'s
        sake. They stretch and contract their bodies constantly and have a habit of stretching across major
        pathways, so you may need to wait for the right moment to pass. This behavior has given them the
        nickname \"traffic lights of the island.\" Be sure to look both ways before your cross.</string>
    <string name="lost_landmark_3">Thief of the Skies</string>
    <string name="lost_landmark_description_3">The undisputed ruler of the skies here is the Klepto. This
        large bird has keen eyesight that enables it to spot prey from far above before swooping down
        to snatch it up in an instant. Once ensnared in its sharp claws, escape is quite difficult, and
        many smaller visitors have been carried off in this way.</string>
    <string name="lost_landmark_4">Ruins Steeped in Mystery</string>
    <string name="lost_landmark_description_4">The purpose of the distinctive ruins scattered throughout
        the island remains unclear. The starburst pattern that appears on them MAY indicate a spot of
        capable of withstanding a great impact. The builders clearly mastered stonework, as these structures
        still operate and move perhaps centuries after their creators had disappeared.</string>
    <string name="lost_landmark_5">Watch Those Hands</string>
    <string name="lost_landmark_description_5">The Trapeetle is a local hazard. Its large hands capture
        prey, who are held tight as the creature explodes in a tragic display seen absolutely nowhere
        else in nature. Best to avoid.</string>
    // Metro Kingdom
    <string name="metro_name">Metro Kingdom</string>
    <string name="metro_moon_count">81</string>
    <string name="metro_regional_count">100</string>
    <string name="metro_landmark_1">Scraping the Sky</string>
    <string name="metro_landmark_description_1">The skyscrapers of New Donk City are most people\'s first
        association with the city. But even among those, New Donk City Hall stands out as the very symbol
        of this great city, so don\'t miss it. Who knows, you might even run into world-renowned Mayor Pauline!</string>
    <string name="metro_landmark_2">A Million-Coin View</string>
    <string name="metro_landmark_description_2">If you\'ve come to New Donk City, you owe it to yourself
        to see it at night. The best viewing spot is the landmark New Donk City Hall, but sadly the interior
        is closed for construction, so you\'ll have to aim for one of the neighboring buildings.\n\nIf it\'s
        festival season, you\'ll have a chance at a once-in-a-lifetime experience, but the timing is a bit
        irregular, so be sure to check the schedule beforehand.</string>
    <string name="metro_landmark_3">Crazy Cap Flagship Store</string>
    <string name="metro_landmark_description_3">There\'s probably only one brand that the entire world
        knows, and that\'s Crazy Cap. Their original flagship store is right here in New Donk City. The
        unique storefront is converted from an old theater. Theater space is no longer much in demand,
        with so many street performers in the city.</string>
    <string name="metro_landmark_4">Always Be Constructing</string>
    <string name="metro_landmark_description_4">New Donkers are used to construction and new developments.
        There\'s always work being done below ground, on rooftops, and inside buildings, so power lines
        never get taken down—they run throughout town. Unaccustomed travelers should watch out for the
        cranes, girders, and manholes scattered everywhere.</string>
    <string name="metro_landmark_5">Scooting Across Town</string>
    <string name="metro_landmark_description_5">These motor scooters may look old-fashioned, but they
        pack a punch and are perfect for tooling around the city. Be sure to try one out!</string>
    // Snow Kingdom
    <string name="snow_name">Snow Kingdom</string>
    <string name="snow_moon_count">55</string>
    <string name="snow_regional_count">50</string>
    <string name="snow_landmark_1">A Frozen Land</string>
    <string name="snow_landmark_description_1">The Snow Kingdom is a world of ice and snow that freezes
        the body but dazzles the eyes. Stay alert, though—one bad step can drop you into the dangerously
        frigid sea. Despite the cold, the town of Shiveria is famous for its warm hospitality, and on
        clear days, the view can\'t be matched.</string>
    <string name="snow_landmark_2">A Warm Community</string>
    <string name="snow_landmark_description_2">Shiveria is a huge excavated settlement beneath the ice.
        It\'s warmer here than up above, but you\'ll want to bundle up all the same.\n\nDespite the cold,
        the cheerful Shiverians will thaw any traveller\'s frozen heart. And if you visit the center square,
        you'll see the fiery passion the Shiverians have for their traditional races. Take one look at
        the screens showing the action, and you\'ll be caught up in the excitement too!</string>
    <string name="snow_landmark_3">Bound Bowl Grand Prix</string>
    <string name="snow_landmark_description_3">THE sporting event is the Bound Bowl Grand Prix. Only
        Shiverians are allowed to participate, but when you watch a race, you\'ll understand why no one
        else COULD participate. Only Shiverian sturdiness could survive a race based on bounding violently
        through the course and crashing into one another. Be sure to see it if you get a chance!</string>
    <string name="snow_landmark_4">Icing and Racing</string>
    <string name="snow_landmark_description_4">Beyond racing, Shiverians are known for elaborate baked goods.
        Especially renowned is the Frost-Frosted Cake, which is very popular at weddings. By tradition,
        only the Shiverian Elder is allowed to make this extraordinary confection. What\'s more, they
        are specifically created as the grand prize for the Bound Bowl Grand Prix, so the only way to
        get one is to convince the winner to let you have it.</string>
    <string name="snow_landmark_5">Crevasse Menace</string>
    <string name="snow_landmark_description_5">Lurking in the local crevasses you may find a Bitefrost.
        These creatures move through the ice under their prey, then thrust upward, chomping. Caution
        (and jumping ability) is advised.</string>
    // Seaside Kingdom
    <string name="seaside_name">Seaside Kingdom</string>
    <string name="seaside_moon_count">71</string>
    <string name="seaside_regional_count">100</string>
    <string name="seaside_landmark_1">Raise a Glass</string>
    <string name="seaside_landmark_description_1">The spectacle known as Glass Tower isn\'t just majestic,
        it also fulfills the critical role of manufacturing the famous local product Sparkle Water.
        \n\nIt stands atop the Glass Palace, which has a uniquely beautiful architectural style. It\'s
        a treasure to be explored!</string>
    <string name="seaside_landmark_2">A Miraculous Mixture</string>
    <string name="seaside_landmark_description_2">The four fountains in Bubblaine spray seawater toward
        the Glass Tower. The ocean here is carbonated but otherwise unremarkable. However, when blended
        in the Glass Tower, it takes on a deep, elegant flavor and becomes Sparkle Water!\n\nThis treasured
        beverage is said to bring good fortune, happiness, and even romance to those who drink it, which
        has led to it being featured in many wedding ceremonies.</string>
    <string name="seaside_landmark_3">A Love Nest for Eels</string>
    <string name="seaside_landmark_description_3">In addition to the fun resort spots found in Bubblaine,
        there are some notable dangerous locations as well. One of these is the underwater cave connected
        to the lighthouse where gigantic creatures called Maw-Rays make their nests and shoot out their
        long bodies in response to stimuli. A little caution can go a long way when exploring this place.</string>
    <string name="seaside_landmark_4">Nature\'s Hot Tub</string>
    <string name="seaside_landmark_description_4">A ways away from the beach sits an outdoor bath fed by
        a natural hot spring. Featuring full ocean views, it has become quite popular with tourists.
        This spring was formed by volcanic activity on the ocean floor, and it\'s said to have numerous
        medicinal effects. Take one dip, and we\'re sure you\'ll fall for its charms. It\'s also a lovely
        natural reprieve from the modern resort developments.</string>
    <string name="seaside_landmark_5">Relaxing Competition</string>
    <string name="seaside_landmark_description_5">When in Bubblaine, be sure to enjoy a game of beach
        volleyball on the local court. The on-site coach gives strong guidance, even for beginners. As
        they say around here, \"Let\'s play!\"</string>
    // Luncheon Kingdom
    <string name="luncheon_name">Luncheon Kingdom</string>
    <string name="luncheon_moon_count">68</string>
    <string name="luncheon_regional_count">100</string>
    <string name="luncheon_landmark_1">Cooking with a Volcano</string>
    <string name="luncheon_landmark_description_1">Surrounded by strange pink lava, Mount Volbono is
        colorful and vibrant, a vision straight from a picture book. It is famous for its cuisine, with
        dishes simmered over the volcano, and chock-full of the local produce that grows to enormous size
        thanks to the volcanic climate.</string>
    <string name="luncheon_landmark_2">The Historic \"Old Town\"</string>
    <string name="luncheon_landmark_description_2">On your way to Mount Volbono, you\'ll pass through the
        Old Town, ringed by the ruined wall that once enclosed the town. These sturdy, cut-stone walls
        even now suggest the prosperity of those times. Atop the walls are little mounds of salt, carried
        by the wind and piled up naturally. Visitors can walk along the tops of the walls—do so if you get
        a chance. The sights here are very different from the colorful scenery of Peronza Plaza, but
        equally breathtaking.</string>
    <string name="luncheon_landmark_3">Cooking Carnival</string>
    <string name="luncheon_landmark_description_3">The highlight of Mount Volbono\'s year is the Cooking
        Carnival, where visitors from all over the world come to sample the famous Stupendous Stew. While
        cooking on a volcano is of course a grand spectacle, the dish itself has a surprisingly delicate
        flavor, described most frequently in reviews as a \"melty deliciousity.\"</string>
    <string name="luncheon_landmark_4">A Resting Place for Meat</string>
    <string name="luncheon_landmark_description_4">The giant slab of meat used in the Stupendous Stew
        is crusted generously in salt and left to rest on a high perch near the volcano. Aging the meat
        high above the lava, cooled by the wind, is essential to creating the core flavor. If you
        arrived before the Cooking Carnival, be sure to take the opportunity to visit the platform and
        see the meat resting soundly before its long journey.</string>
    <string name="luncheon_landmark_5">Peronza Plaza</string>
    <string name="luncheon_landmark_description_5">Be sure to visit the centrally located Peronza Plaza
        for a friendly welcome. Once among the colorful heaps of giant ingredients and succulent smells,
        you may find it hard to leave.</string>
    // Ruined Kingdom
    <string name="ruined_name">Ruined Kingdom</string>
    <string name="ruined_moon_count">10</string>
    <string name="ruined_landmark_1">Reaching for the Heavens</string>
    <string name="ruined_landmark_description_1">This tower once collected energy from lightning in the
        thunderclouds that constantly swirl here. Some say it was destroyed by repeated lightning strikes,
        but others note the unnatural shapes into which the tower crumbled and wonder if it fell into
        ruin for different reasons entirely.</string>
    <string name="ruined_landmark_2">High Stakes</string>
    <string name="ruined_landmark_description_2">Amid the ruins, these swords surely stand out. They\'re
        thought to be left over from a large battle here in Crumbleden. One certainly feels a sense of
        intentionality in the way they\'re stuck straight down, as if fallen from the sky. Some see them
        not as swords, but rather nails or stakes. Perhaps the eyelets at the top allowed ropes or chains
        through to anchor something, but it's impossible to say what.</string>
    <string name="ruined_landmark_3">Ruined Dreams</string>
    <string name="ruined_landmark_description_3">It\'s only because of the people of Crumbleden\'s skill
        in construction that there are ruins left here to see. Their building style was reliable and
        straightforward, but whatever they\'d hoped to accomplish by harnessing the fearsome power of
        lightning remains unclear. Some have theorized that the circular plaza atop the tower was built
        for a standoff of some kind.</string>
    <string name="ruined_landmark_4">The Great Altar</string>
    <string name="ruined_landmark_description_4">It\'s thought that this altar was built so this former
        kingdom could communicate with (or perhaps confront) something. This is the only altar built here,
        and scholars have been keen to discover its intent. It\'s also said to be shaped like something
        in particular. The idea that it was meant to charge lightning has been disproved. The new theory
        is that it was built to call something down and then restrain the lightning.</string>
    <string name="ruined_landmark_5">Are Those…Claw Marks?</string>
    <string name="ruined_landmark_description_5">The stone here has numerous large slashes cut through
        it, often in parallel tracks suggesting giant claws. But that can\'t be right—what could claw
        through stone?</string>
    // Bowser's Kingdom
    <string name="bowsers_name">Bowser\'s Kingdom</string>
    <string name="bowsers_moon_count">62</string>
    <string name="bowsers_regional_count">100</string>
    <string name="bowsers_landmark_1">Terrifying Gatekeepers</string>
    <string name="bowsers_landmark_description_1">Don\'t run afoul of the Stairface Ogres that guard this
        kingdom. When they spot an intruder, they bring their huge mallets down, no questions asked.
        On the other hand, you have to admire their tenacity and work ethic. The scars on their faces
        show they don\'t give up easily.</string>
    <string name="bowsers_landmark_2">Beautiful Tile Work</string>
    <string name="bowsers_landmark_description_2">This kingdom\'s architecture is unique. Roofs are made
        of heavy, layered tiles that will not budge even if walked upon. They also create a uniformity in
        the overall design, enhancing the beauty of the palace.\n\nThough you can move along the roofs,
        this palace rests quite high in the sky, and if you fall off, you will most definitely die.
        It\'s not the surest footing either, so be careful.</string>
    <string name="bowsers_landmark_3">Statues Guard the Court</string>
    <string name="bowsers_landmark_description_3">The palace tower highlights the inner citadel, and the
        gate leading to it is guarded by fearsome statues. The statues are fashioned after gods of wind
        and thunder, the perfect motif for a sky palace, and since they are modeled on Bowser, the ruler
        of this kingdom, they serve as a warning to foes here and abroad.</string>
    <string name="bowsers_landmark_4">Impressive Fortifications</string>
    <string name="bowsers_landmark_description_4">Surrounding the inner citadel are the second and third
        courts. The second court is especially fortified, with many cannons to repel invaders. Cannonballs
        often roll along the ground, and many tourists fall trying to evade them. Legends speak of invaders
        repelling the cannonballs with spears, but no mere mortal could hope to do this, so try not
        to get too close!</string>
    <string name="bowsers_landmark_5">An Oasis of Calm</string>
    <string name="bowsers_landmark_description_5">This elegant garden is a balm for the brutality of
        this kingdom and will help you forget all the hardships you faced to reach it. You can even buy
        souvenirs, so be sure you stop by!</string>
    // Moon Kingdom
    <string name="moon_name">Moon Kingdom</string>
    <string name="moon_moon_count">38</string>
    <string name="moon_regional_count">50</string>
    <string name="moon_landmark_1">Wedding Hall</string>
    <string name="moon_landmark_description_1">Legends tell of a moon goddess, and this wedding hall
        is said to have been created in her honor, though no one knows for sure. The stunning exterior
        contrasts beautifully with the black sky, a symbol of Honeylune Ridge. Weddings here are often
        open, so lucky travelers can join the party.</string>
    <string name="moon_landmark_2">Lunar Life Forms</string>
    <string name="moon_landmark_description_2">The surface of the moon is harsh, but a few creatures do
        live there. Take heed if tempted to study their unique shape and movement up close, as they have
        sharp spikes. it\'s probably best to observe them from a safe vantage point.\n\nInterestingly,
        similar creatures can be found in the Seaside Kingdom. Did life on our planet (which began in the
        seas) actually originate on the moon?</string>
    <string name="moon_landmark_3">Cubes of Mystery</string>
    <string name="moon_landmark_description_3">Possessing unique metallic properties, it\'s hard to imagine
        how these cubic Moon Rocks formed naturally, but they can be found in great abundance up here.
        Similar rocks have also been found in various areas on the planet, and the method of their formation
        remains shrouded in mystery. We recommend seeking one out and pondering its mysteries up close!</string>
    <string name="moon_landmark_4">Lunar Interior: Secrets</string>
    <string name="moon_landmark_description_4">We\'ve heard stories about extensive caverns beneath the
        lunar interior. There\'s an entrance directly into the moon rock that\'s easily accessed, but it
        sounds quite dangerous inside.\n\nOn the other hand, tales abound of thrills and mysteries waiting
        within, so it may be worth investigating. Be sure to take the necessary precautions before
        you go, though!</string>
    <string name="moon_landmark_5">A View to Remember</string>
    <string name="moon_landmark_description_5">Our world as seen from the Wedding Hall is something everyone
        needs to experience at least once in their life. With the planet as your witness, it\'s no wonder
        weddings are held here.</string>
    // Mushroom Kingdom
    <string name="mushroom_name">Mushroom Kingdom</string>
    <string name="mushroom_moon_count">104</string>
    <string name="mushroom_regional_count">100</string>
    <string name="mushroom_landmark_1">A Lovely Portrait in Glass</string>
    <string name="mushroom_landmark_description_1">Because Princess Peach is so often absent from her kingdom,
        her citizens took it upon themselves to create a stained-glass portrait of her on the castle balcony.
        While a pale reflection of the genuine article, the portrait brings comfort to the citizenry when
        their princess can't be with them.</string>
    <string name="mushroom_landmark_2">Towering Mysteries</string>
    <string name="mushroom_landmark_description_2">In older times, the towers dotting the landscape here
        were watchtowers. Now they hold and preserve a series of mysterious paintings. These incredibly
        detailed works are so real that admirers speak of being pulled into another world by the
        paintings.\n\nHowever, it\'s extremely rare for tourists to be permitted to see them, due to
        some undescribed danger, and casual visits are discouraged.</string>
    <string name="mushroom_landmark_3">Places to Relax</string>
    <string name="mushroom_landmark_description_3">The Toads of the Mushroom Kingdom value their relaxation
        and have created several lovely spots on the castle grounds for that purpose. Neither too small
        nor too large, and with just the right amount of ornamentation, these plazas and courtyards exemplify
        the best traits of this kingdom.</string>
    <string name="mushroom_landmark_4">Slightly Scary Woods</string>
    <string name="mushroom_landmark_description_4">Even the serene Mushroom Kingdom has its more dangerous
        locales. This forest was originally planted for mushroom cultivation, but while the mushrooms
        have flourished, a large number of wild Goombas have also moved in. While it\'s come to be known
        as Goomba Woods, it\'s still a pleasant place for a stroll, so if you\'re not afraid of these
        fearsome beasts, why not treat yourself to a walk?</string>
    <string name="mushroom_landmark_5">A Castle\'s Water Feature</string>
    <string name="mushroom_landmark_description_5">The only lake on the castle grounds features a small
        but lovely waterfall and is a popular spot to visit. The lake formed naturally, but some claim
        that its shape is familiar. Hmm…</string>
</resources>